[{"stepName": "Identify Motion of objects", "stepNumber": 1, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "How many moving objects are present?", "options": [3, 5, 0, 6], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "motion", "threejssubstep": 0, "threejssubsubstep": -1, "tobeshown": 1, "show1": [""], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "How many strings are there?", "options": [5, 0, 4, 2], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "motion", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 0, "tobeshown": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}]}, {"stepName": "Write FBD equation for each Moving block", "stepNumber": 2, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2081+30=0", "-N\u2081-30=0", "-N\u2081+30=0", "+N\u2081-30=0"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0"], "showfc": ["N\u2081: Normal between red block and Big block", "T\u2081: Tension in pink string"], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is the direction of normal reaction on block 1 due to B?", "options": ["N1perpendicular up", "N1perpendicular down"], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "answer": 0, "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"]}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for red block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "answer": 1}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on red block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2081 rightwards", "T\u2081 leftwards"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2081+30=0", "-N\u2081-30=0", "-N\u2081+30=0", "+N\u2081-30=0"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N1, ", "Downward Forces: 30", "Rightward Forces: T\u2081, ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the x-direction", "options": ["+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "showfc": ["N\u2081: Normal between red block and Big block", "T\u2081: Tension in pink string"], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the x-direction", "options": ["+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N1, ", "Downward Forces: 30", "Rightward Forces: T\u2081, ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "+40+T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-40+T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["T\u2082: Tension in red string"], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for yellow block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "answer": 1}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on yellow block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2082 upwards", "T\u2082 downwards"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "+40+T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-40+T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: T\u2082, ", "Downward Forces: 40", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of first pulley in the x-direction", "options": ["-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "+2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "showfc": ["T\u2081: Tension in pink string", "T\u2082: Tension in red string"], "showfcheading": ["First pulley"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for first pulley cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["First pulley"], "answer": 3}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on first pulley?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2081 rightwards", "T\u2081 leftwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["First pulley"]}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on first pulley?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2081 rightwards", "T\u2081 leftwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: T\u2081, "], "showfcheading": ["First pulley"]}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on first pulley?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2082 rightwards", "T\u2082 leftwards"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 3, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: T\u2081, T\u2081, "], "showfcheading": ["First pulley"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of first pulley in the x-direction", "options": ["-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "+2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: T\u2082, ", "Leftward Forces: T\u2081, T\u2081, "], "showfcheading": ["First pulley"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"]}]}, {"stepName": "Constraint Equations", "stepNumber": 3, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "What is the constraint equation for pink string?", "options": ["+a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0", "+a\u2081x-2.0a\u2083=0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0", "-a\u2081x-2.0a\u2083=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": [], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is the number of parts which change length in the pink string?", "options": [5, 4, 2, 3], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": [], "tobeshown": 0}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for pink string:", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2083", "-a\u2083"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for pink string:", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2081", "-a\u2081"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is net double derivative of change in l\u2081 for pink string:", "options": ["+a\u2083-a\u2081", "+a\u2083+a\u2081", "-a\u2083+a\u2081", "-a\u2083-a\u2081"], "answer": [0], "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": [], "tobeshown": 0}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2082 for pink string:", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2083", "-a\u2083"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for pink string?", "options": ["+a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0", "+a\u2081x-2.0a\u2083=0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0", "-a\u2081x-2.0a\u2083=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0", "+a\u2082-a\u2083=0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": [], "tobeshown": 0}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for red string?", "options": ["+a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "+a\u2082-a\u2083=0", "-a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "-a\u2082-a\u2083=0"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0", "+a\u2082-a\u2083=0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": [], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is the number of parts which change length in the red string?", "options": [5, 4, 2, 3], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": [], "tobeshown": 0}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for red string:", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2083", "-a\u2083"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2082 for red string:", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2082", "-a\u2082"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for red string?", "options": ["+a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "+a\u2082-a\u2083=0", "-a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "-a\u2082-a\u2083=0"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+N\u2081-30=0", "+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081x", "+40-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-a\u2081x+2.0a\u2083=0", "+a\u2082-a\u2083=0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": [], "tobeshown": 0}]}]